<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Yu-Wen Chen</title>
    <link>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Yu-Wen Chen</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year} Yu-Wen Chen </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intercomparison of aircraft and ground based measurements near major pollution sources over Taiwan (Ongoing)</title>
      <link>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/measurement_intercomparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/measurement_intercomparison/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, we focus on the pollutions near major sources over western Taiwan.
Aircraft-based observation data are analyzed and compared with surface measurements to investigate near surface chemical reactions of pollutants.
The result will be presented in 18th ACC in Taipei in Dec. 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aircraft-baed observation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ground-based measurements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sounding and Lidar data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reanalysis data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracer distribution simulation in western Taiwan using high resolution Taiwan Vector Vorticity Model (Ongoing)</title>
      <link>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/tracer_transport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/tracer_transport/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this project, I analyzed simulation results and evaluated the impact on target regions, which usually have terrible air pollutions. In the next stage, we aim to applied zero and first-order chemical reactions into the model to inspect lifetime effect on the regions so as to understand the sources of the pollutant in those highly-polluted regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taiwan Vector Vorticity Modeling results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ground-based measurements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantitation of glucose using Cu₂O/Ag nanoparticles probe with a smartphone-controlled portable device</title>
      <link>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/glucose_quantification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/glucose_quantification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A single-step method combining material preparation and the actual glucose measurements via the in situ growth of Cu&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O/Ag nanoparticles was reported. Mechanistically, I use glucose itself to reduce Cu&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2+&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; and Ag&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;+&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; ions that are stabilized with 3-mercaptopropionic acid and bovine serum albumin under alkaline conditions to form Cu&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O/Ag nanoparticles and produce a color change in solution due to plasmonic resonance at 400 nm, which can be related back to the concentration of glucose. This was also the research of my master thesis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing mercury ions from polluted solution through poly-dopamine-modified Fe₃O₄ nanoparticles</title>
      <link>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/mercury_removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ywchen-tw.github.io/project/mercury_removal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this study, I improved the production efficiency of Fe&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;3&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;4&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; nanoparticles by using a novel microwave synthesizer. Also, by modifying a poly-dopamine layer on the surface of nanoparticles to increase the surface area of nanoparticles, I succeeded in enlarging the Hg&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;2+&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; ions adsorption capacity and releasing efficiency under hydrochloric acid of poly-dopamine-modified Fe&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;3&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;4&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; nanoparticles and maintaining the high magnetic property of the material. The magnetic property of poly-dopamine-modified Fe&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;3&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;O&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;4&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; nanoparticles makes it eco-friendly to reuse the material.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
